That is the reality of the world that we live in, where there's some of us that do what we do with free media, free media, meaning we're not in the ecosystem of mainstream.
We're not controlled by brands or corporate.
We literally wake up every day and sit the course of the work that we're going to do and the vision that we have, whether people like it or not.
And this is a click based business.
It's a comment and engagement based business.
And so whatever drives the comments drives the bag.
And that's a really scary thing if you don't have discipline or some type of moral authority.
Thank you.
If you don't have ethics.
If you don't have ethics and you can make a lot of money, but you can do a lot of harm.
But don't you feel like that's kind of like to me, like that's the foundation of it.
It's like you already have to have a certain give and take with your ethics to be like, you know what?
I'm going to start a business based on telling other people's business because it makes it to where you now get to become the judge and jury about what you think people need to know about other people.